<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<section id="2534">
  <number>0</number>
  <name></name>
  <summary>&lt;p dir="ltr" style="text-align: left;"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Welcome to Teaching Adult English Learners: Principles and Practices&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;em&gt;This course and the accompanying materials were developed by Betsy Parrish of Hamline University.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;This course will take 3.5 hours to complete, and you must complete all assessments and knowledge checks to earn a certificate.&lt;span style="font-size: 1.7rem;"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;This course is designed to support teachers new to working with adult English learners, or ELs. After completing the course, you will be able to identify and apply appropriate instructional strategies for teaching adult ELs. You will also have strengthened your skills as an instructor and be able to implement classroom management practices to optimize learning in both in-person and virtual learning environments.&amp;nbsp;​&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;em style="font-size: 1.7rem;"&gt;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;em&gt;Disclaimer: &lt;/em&gt;&lt;em&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;span style=""&gt;This
course was developed&lt;/span&gt; under contract with &lt;span style=""&gt;the American Institutes for
Research (AIR)&lt;/span&gt; with funding from the U.S. Department of Education (ED),
Office of Career, Technical, and Adult Education (OCTAE), under Contract No. &lt;span style=""&gt;91990020F0340&lt;/span&gt;.
The &lt;span style=""&gt;content and &lt;/span&gt;opinions expressed herein do not necessarily represent
the positions or policies of the U.S. Department of Education, and no official
endorsement by the U.S. Department of Education should be inferred.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;span style="font-size: 1.7rem; font-style: italic;"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;After completing this course, you will be able to:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;describe factors that affect learning for adult ELs and identify learner needs,&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;identify and apply appropriate instructional strategies for teaching adult ELs, and&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&amp;nbsp;implement classroom management practices to optimize learning.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;This course is composed of these units:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;Introduction&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Units 1–5&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Conclusion&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;This is the main course page. Each unit of the course below includes printable resources, sample lesson plans, and resource lists with links to websites, videos, and other materials to enhance your learning experience.&amp;nbsp;&lt;p&gt;Please note, items with solid boxes can be self-checked to indicate completion; however, the pre-course and post-course assessments are graded and required for completion.&amp;nbsp;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong style="font-size: 1.7rem;"&gt;To begin, select Introduction below.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</summary>
  <summaryformat>1</summaryformat>
  <sequence>8927</sequence>
  <visible>1</visible>
  <availabilityjson>{"op":"&amp;","c":[],"showc":[]}</availabilityjson>
  <timemodified>1647956985</timemodified>
</section>